(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ぺこーらありがとうLive
Pekora Arigato Live
2019. 7. 17
ぺこーらありがとうLive
Pekora "Arigatou" Live
サクラがさくよ
The cherry blossoms are blooming
見なれたいつもの坂道に
On the familiar slope we always take
あぁ 別れを
Ah, this farewell...
さよならメモリーズ
作詞・作曲 ryo
Sayonara Memories
Lyrics/Composition: ryo
泣いて笑った
We cried and laughed
あの日々 なんだか昨日のことのよう
Those days somehow seem like only yesterday
この道はそう
This road, yes
未来へ続く道
Is a road leading to the future
そんな気がしたの
That's how I felt
例年より早い開花
The blossoms opened earlier than usual this year
そう 君は嬉しがってた
Yeah, you were so happy about it
私は笑って「そうだね」って言った
I laughed and said, "You're right"
あと少ししたらもう ここには戻れないのに
Even though in just a little while,
we won't be able to come back here anymore
言葉じゃうまく言えない想い
These feelings I can't put into words well
君に打ち明けるとしたらなんて
If I were to confess them to you, what would I say?
伝えよう
I'll tell you
最初で最後
For the first and last time
一緒に帰った道は 私にとって特別な思い出
The road we walked home together
is a special memory for me
忘れないよ さよならメモリーズ
I'll never forget. Farewell memories
春が来たら それぞれの道を
When spring comes, we'll each go our separate ways
また会える日を願って
Hoping for the day we can meet again
「さよなら」小さくつぶやいた
I whispered "Goodbye" softly
空はあの日と変わらず青くて
The sky was as blue as it was that day
だからちょっと泣けた
So I cried a little bit
わざと遠回りしたの
I purposefully took the long way around
少しでも長く君の隣にいたくて
Because I wanted to be by your side
for just a little longer
私はおどけて「間違えた」って言った
I joked around and said I took the wrong turn
君は笑う その顔がまぶしくて目をそらした
You laughed, and your face was so radiant
that I looked away
言葉じゃうまく言えない想い
These feelings I can't put into words well
胸に抱いてこの道を歩いた
Carrying them in my heart, I walked this road
覚えてる あの時君は
I remember... at that time, you
私の名前を呼んでくれた
Called my name
二人 夕暮れの帰り道で 忘れないよ さよならメモリーズ
On the road home at dusk, just the two of us
I'll never forget. Farewell memories
出会えたこと 感謝してる
I'm grateful that we met
初めて見た 満開のサクラ
The full-blown cherry blossoms
I saw for the first time
あれからどれくらい変われたんだろう
I wonder how much I've changed since then
櫻並木のあの人のこと好きになりそうで
I think I'm starting to fall for that person under the cherry blossoms
なんでかな わかんないよ
I don't know why, I just don't know
それからの毎日はとても楽しくてだけど同じくらいに
Every day since then has been so much fun, but at the same time
つらかったんだ
It's been just as painful
ごめんね なんかうまく言えないよ
I'm sorry, I can't seem to say it right
だから私 君となんていうか
So I... with you, how should I put it
今のまま
As things are now...
サヨナラしたくないの
I don't want to say goodbye
友達のままじゃ
Staying just as friends...
もういやなの
...I don't want that anymore
言おうと思ってた
I've been meaning to tell you
私 君の
That I... of you...
君のことずっと ずっと
That I've always, always...
前から
...from a long time ago
好きでした
Loved you
やっと言えた
I finally said it
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ありがとう
Thank you
ちょっと待ったー！
Wait a second!
ぺこちゃん やめへんでー！
Peko-chan isn't quitting!
兎田一番！
Usada is Number One!
耳にも見える 兎田の帽子
Usada's hat even looks like ears
行くぞ兎田 己のために
Go, Usada! For your own sake
夢はでかいぜ 世界征服
My dream is big: world domination
目指せ兎田 己のために
Aim high, Usada! For your own sake
兎田一番！
Usada is Number One!
あの日誓った 約束の地へ
To the promised land we swore to reach that day
進め兎田 己のために
Forge ahead, Usada! For your own sake
たとえ嵐が 吹き荒れるとも
Even if a storm comes raging through
目指せ兎田 己のために
Aim high, Usada! For your own sake
Are you ready?
Yeah!
Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Woo!
あいつもこいつもあの席を
Everyone's eyeing that seat
ただひとつねらっているんだよ
Aiming for that one spot
このクラスで一番の美人の隣を
Next to the prettiest girl in class
ああ みんなライバルさ
Ah, everyone's a rival
ライバルさ
Rival
ああ 命がけだよ
Ah, I'll bet my life
イェイ イェイ イェイ
Yay yay yay
運命の女神さまよ
Goddess of fate
このぼくにほほえんで一度だけでも
Smile at me, even if just once
Wow wow wow...
勉強する気もしない気も
No motivation to study
この時にかかっているんだよ
It all depends on this moment
もしだめならこのぼくは
If it's no good, then I'll...
もうぐれてしまうよ
Go astray
Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Woo!
二枚目気どりの秀才や
The guy acting cool
あのいやな悪党番長も
And that annoying bully leader
胸はずませ待っている
With hearts racing, they wait
どの席になるか
To see which seat they get
ああ あの横顔
Ah, that profile
横顔
Profile
ああ みつめられたら
Ah, if she looks at me
イェイ イェイ イェイ
Yay yay yay
授業中は天国だよ
During class, it's heaven
このぼくに幸せをあたえておくれ
Please grant me happiness
勉強する気もしない気も
No motivation to study
この時にかかっているんだよ
It all depends on this moment
もしだめならこのぼくは
If it's no good, then I'll...
もうぐれてしまうよ
Go astray
Hey!
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love
光の矢胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces my heart
君をわかりたいんだよ
I want to understand you
ねえ 教えて
Hey, tell me
すれ違う言葉にちょっとだけの後悔
Regretting the words that missed each other
涙こぼれて
Tears overflow
忙しい感情鼓動にリンクする
Busy emotions link to my heartbeat
チューニング確かめたいんだ
I want to check our tuning
目的ばかりにとらわれて
Being caught up only in the goal
大事なものが霞んで逃げて
Important things blur and escape
今日もリスタート
Restarting again today
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love
落ちている
...is falling in love.
光の矢胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces my chest.
全部わかりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything.
ねえ
Hey...
聞かせて
Tell me.
たった1ミリが遠くて
Even just one millimeter feels so far.
駆け抜けた日々に
In the days I've run through.
忘れない 忘れられない
I won't forget, I can't forget.
輝く1ページ
This one shining page.
お似合いの二人に なんだか複雑な
Looking at the perfect couple, I feel complicated.
気持ちがいるよ
These feelings are here.
初めての感情 鼓動にリンクする
This first-time emotion links to my heartbeat.
体温計 壊れちゃったかな?
I wonder if the thermometer broke?
自分のことわからないまま
Without even understanding myself.
あの子にアドバイスまでしちゃって
I even ended up giving advice to that girl.
胸が痛いや
My chest hurts.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love.
光の矢胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces my chest.
気付いたこの想いは もう遅いの
Is it already too late for these feelings I've realized?
あの子のほうが可愛いの 知ってるよ だけど
I know she's cuter than me, but...
うまくいくななんてね
Hoping things don't go well for them...
逃げ出したいくせに
Even though I want to run away.
バカ。
Stupid.
君のこと全部わかりたいって思っちゃう
I end up thinking I want to understand everything about you.
これが恋だって初めて気付いたの
I realized for the first time that this is love.
絶対 振り向いてほしい
I definitely want you to look my way.
遅かったけど諦めたくない
It's late, but I don't want to give up.
だって 好きだから
Because... I love you.
本当に 咲いた 花が 恋をした
A flower that truly bloomed fell in love.
花は 必死に 上を向いて 笑った
The flower desperately looked up and smiled.
青い 夏の 蕾も 恋をした
The blue summer bud also fell in love.
咲かない 花と 火薬の 匂い
The flower that won't bloom and the smell of gunpowder.
本当の気持ち 言葉にして
Putting my true feelings into words.
大事なこと話せたら
If I could talk about what's important.
今日もリスタート
Starting over again today.
どんだけ鈍い君だから 口に出して言わなきゃ
Since you're so dense, I have to say it out loud.
今君に伝えるよ ねえ 好きです
I'm telling you right now. Hey, I love you.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love.
光の矢胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces my chest.
全部わかりたいんだよ ねえ
I want to understand everything, hey.
聞かせて
Tell me.
たぐり寄せて 0センチ
Pulling it closer, zero centimeters.
駆け抜けた日々に
In the days I've run through.
忘れない 忘れられない
I won't forget, I can't forget.
輝く1ページ
This one shining page.
ハッピープレゼント
Happy Present
黒板そっぽ向いて
Facing away from the blackboard.
ちらり見つめる先は
The destination of my sidelong glances is...
甘い横顔ファンタジー
...the fantasy of your sweet profile.
突然校舎裏
Suddenly behind the school building.
そうだ恋愛モード
That's right, romance mode.
やっぱ私じゃない
As I thought, it's not me.
だけどあなた...
But you...
ハッピー・プレゼント
Happy Present
健気に頑張る
Working hard with all my heart
いつの日か
That one day...
振り向かせてみせるわ
I'll make you turn around and look at me!
鈍感すぎなのよ　御身さん
You're just too dense, you!
Happy Happy Happy Present
あなたにHappy Present
A Happy Present for you
わかってほしいの　この気持ち
I want you to understand these feelings
あなただけよ　永遠のワンス
It's only you, my eternal "once"
Happy Happy Happy Present
あなたに全部捧げる I love you
I'll give you everything, I love you
いつか終わるの？
Will it end someday?
ねぇ　抱きしめてほしい
Hey, I want you to hold me
片想い
Unrequited love
まとめて　ため息色
All together, the color of a sigh
不意に見つめる先に
Suddenly, where you're looking...
暗い横顔　ミステリアス
...your dark profile is mysterious
走る渡り廊下
Running through the connecting corridor
背中押す　全力モード
Pushing your back, in full-power mode
もしかして　振られたの？
Could it be that you got dumped?
元気出してよ
Cheer up!
私がいるよ
I'm here for you!
告白だよ　でも気づいてない顔
It's a confession, but you're not noticing
鈍感すぎよ　御身さん
You're just too dense, you!
ときめきHappy Present
Heart-throbbing Happy Present
ドキドキもっとPresent
More heart-pounding Presents
気づいてほしいの　胸の鼓動
I want you to notice my heartbeat
奏でてるよ　恋のメロディ
It's playing a melody of love
ときめきHappy Present
Heart-throbbing Happy Present
あなたに全部捧げる I want you
I'll give you everything, I want you
いつになるだろう？
When will it be?
ねぇ　終わらせたいよ
Hey, I want to end it
片想い
Unrequited love
花の塔
Tower of Flower
君が持ってきた漫画
The manga you brought over
くれた知らない名前のお花
The flower with the name I didn't know that you gave me
今日はまだ来ないかな
I wonder if you won't come today either
初めての感情知ってしまった
I've come to know a feeling for the first time
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって
Tracing the painting decorated on the window
一人で宇宙を旅して
Traveling through space all by myself
それだけでいいはずだったのに
That should have been enough, and yet...
君の手を握ってしまったら
If I were to end up holding your hand
孤独を知らないこの街には
In this town that doesn't know loneliness...
もう二度と帰ってくることはできないのでしょう
...I probably won't be able to return ever again
君が手を差し伸べた
You reached out your hand
光で影が生まれる
Shadows are born from the light
歌って聴かせて
Sing it for me
この話の続き
The rest of this story
連れて行って見たことない星まで
Take me away, to a star I've never seen before
誰の手の声も届かない
Where no one's hands or voices can reach
高くそびえ立った塔の上
Atop the tower that stands tall
飛ばす風船　風連れ
Letting balloons fly, carried by the wind
僕を君に
For you...
まだ笑ってほしいんだ
...I want you to keep smiling.
満たされない穴は
The unfilled holes in my heart
脱線の会話や
Were filled by derailed conversations
澄ましたポーズで
And straight-faced poses
これまでは埋めてきたけど
That's how I've survived until now
退屈な日々を蹴飛ばして
Kicking away those boring days
君と二人で
Just the two of us
この街中を
Through this whole city
泳げたらそれはどれだけ
If we could swim, how much...
素敵なことでしょう？
...wonderful that would be?
出したことないほど大きな
With a voice louder than ever before
声でやっと君に伝わる
It'll finally reach you
歪な声がきっとちょうどいいさ
This distorted voice is surely just right
世界の端と端を結んで
Connecting the ends of the world
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって
Tracing the paintings on the window
一人で宇宙を旅して
Traveling the universe all alone
それだけでも不自由ないけど
I had no complaints about that, but...
僕は選んでみたいのさ
I want to try choosing
逆様な心の空を
The sky of an inverted heart
安全なループを今、
This safe loop, right now,
書き換えて！
Rewrite it!
君の手を握りしめたら
Once I hold your hand tight
孤独を知らないこの街には
To this city that knows no loneliness
もう二度と帰ってくることはできないのでしょう
We probably won't be able to return ever again
いくらでも迷いながら
Even if we get lost as many times as it takes
光も影も見に行こう
Let's go see both the light and the shadows
歌って聞かせてこの話の続き
Sing to me the rest of this story
連れて行って見たことない星まで
Take me to stars I've never seen before
世界の端と端を結んで
Connecting the ends of the world
つっぱることが男の
Being a rebel is a man's...
たった一つの勲章だって
...only true badge of honor
この胸に信じて生きてきた
That's what I've believed in all my life
泣きたくなるようなつらい時もあるけど
There are times so painful I want to cry
いつも俺達がんばってきた
But we've always kept on fighting
時の重さに流されそうになった時らも
Even when the weight of time tried to sweep us away
歯をくいしばりたえてきた
We gritted our teeth and endured
ガキの頃路地裏で見た
In the back alleys of our youth
夜空にキラめいていた
Sparkling in the night sky
流れる星を見て
Looking up at the shooting stars
誓った思いを忘れちゃいないぜ
I haven't forgotten the oath I made
つっぱることが男の
Being a rebel is a man's...
たった一つの勲章だって
...only true badge of honor
この胸に信じて生きてきた
That's what I've believed in all my life
氷のように冷たい世間の壁が
The cold, ice-like walls of society
いつもさえぎる俺たちの前を
Are always blocking our path
胸にえがいたこの夢はハンパじゃないから
Because this dream in my heart is no half-measure
かじかむこの手握りしめ
Grasping these numbing hands tight
ガキの頃赤トンボ
Like back when we were kids
追いかけてた時の
Chasing after the red dragonflies
瞳は...
Eyes...
今でも俺たちは忘れちゃいないぜ
Even now, we haven't forgotten
つっぱることが男の たった一つの勲章だって
That acting tough is a man's one and only medal
この胸に信じて生きて
Living with this belief in our hearts
つっぱることが男の たった一つの勲章だって
That acting tough is a man's one and only medal
この胸に信じて生きて行く
Living with this belief in our hearts
つっぱることが男の たった一つの勲章だって
That acting tough is a man's one and only medal
この胸に信じて生きて行く
Living with this belief in our hearts
もうすぐ時計は9時
Soon the clock will strike nine
もうそこに一番星
And there's the first star of the evening
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる
I step on my shadow, wanting to disappear into the night
帰り道
On my way home
どんなに探してみても
No matter how hard I search
一つしかない星
There's only one star
何億光年 離れたところから
From hundreds of millions of light-years away
あんなに輝く
It shines so brightly
いいな 君は
Must be nice, you
みんなから愛されて
Are loved by everyone
いいや 僕は
No, me
ずっと一人きりさ
I've always been all alone
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
星降る夜 一瞬の願い事
A wish in a moment on a night of falling stars
きらめいて ゆらめいて
Sparkling, wavering
震えてるシグナル
A trembling signal
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
空見上げて 指を差されるような
Like being pointed at while looking up at the sky
つないだ線 解かないで
Please don't undo the lines connecting us
僕がどんなに 眩しくても
No matter how bright I might be
もうすぐ時計は8時
Soon the clock will strike eight
夜空に満天の星
The night sky is full of stars
何億光年 離れたところには
In a place hundreds of millions of light-years away
もうないかもしれない
They might not even exist anymore
月が綺麗で
The moon is so beautiful
泣きそうになるのは
The reason I feel like crying
いつの日にか
Is because someday
別れが来るから
A parting will surely come
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
彗星みたい 流れるひとりごと
A monologue flowing like a comet
消えていく 残像は
The disappearing afterimages are
真夜中のプリズム
A midnight prism
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
切なる願い 誰かに届いたら
If my earnest wish could reach someone
変われるかな 夜の淵を
I wonder if I can change
なぞるような こんな僕でも
Tracing the edge of the night, even for someone like me
遥か彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった
In the far distance, we ended up meeting
カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまうよ
It's karma, so we'll keep meeting over and over
雲の隙間で
Through the gaps in the clouds
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
夜広げて 描こう絵空事
Spread out the night and let's draw a pipe dream
暗闇を 照らすような
Like something that lights up the darkness
満月じゃなくても
Even if it's not a full moon
…なくても
...even if not
だから集まって星座になりたい
So I want us to gather and become a constellation
色とりどりの光放つような
Like emitting multi-colored light
つないだ線　解かないよ
I won't unravel the lines we've connected
君がどんなに眩しくても
No matter how dazzling you are
君じゃなきゃダメみたい
It seems it has to be you
なんか今日のなんかすごく優しくて
Something about today is something so kind
君じゃなきゃダメみたい
It seems it has to be you
こちらとしてはそのつもりないけど
I don't intend it to be that way, but...
君じゃなきゃダメみたい
It seems it has to be you
バレバレじゃん　デカく出てるじゃん　それ
It's so obvious, it's showing up big, that...
君じゃなきゃダメみたい
It seems it has to be you
頭の中お花畑だとか少女漫画だとか
Flower fields in the head, shoujo manga
もうなにしたってどうだっていい
Whatever I do, it doesn't matter
そう今すぐ君に会いたい
Yes, I want to see you right now
君に会って確かめてみたい
I want to meet you and find out for sure
世界のことわり　愛の定義
The logic of the world, the definition of love
幸せのカテゴリー
The category of happiness
まだまだ君を知りたい
I still want to know you more
こんなセリフ柄でもないけど
A line like this isn't my style, but...
どんなに格好つけてたって始まりやしない
No matter how much I act cool, nothing will start
君じゃなきゃダメみたい
It seems it has to be you
今ごろになって気づいたところでさ
Even if I've noticed it by now
君じゃなきゃ意味がない
It has no meaning unless it's you
明日も嫌でも訪れるわけだけど
Even if tomorrow comes whether I like it or not
君じゃなきゃ意味がない
It has no meaning unless it's you
分かってんじゃん　デカく期待してんじゃん　それ
You understand, don't you? You're expecting a lot, that...
君じゃなきゃ意味がない
It has no meaning unless it's you
その際うわさ話だとかご近所付き合いだとか
At that point, rumors or neighborhood relations
もうなりふり構ってらんない
I can't care about appearances
そう確かに君しかいない
Yes, certainly there is only you
君だけにはありのままいたい
I want to be as I am only with you
笑い転げたり　愚痴たれたり
Rolling with laughter, or complaining
泣きべそ強がったり
Crying, or acting tough
この世でただ一人みたい
Like the only one in this world
自分でも笑っちゃうんですけど
Even I laugh at myself
他の誰かじゃもう満たされやしない
I can't be satisfied by anyone else anymore
君じゃなきゃ意味がない
It has no meaning unless it's you
さんざん迷って壁に当たって
Wandering so much and hitting a wall
まるで心は君への迷路
It's like my heart is a maze leading to you
考えすぎて道もはぐれて
Thinking too much and being led off the path
右だ左だ全部初歩的(トラップ)さ
Right, left, it's all elementary (a trap)
もう何だってどうだっていい　そう
Whatever happens, it's fine, yes
今すぐ君に会いたい
I want to see you right now
君に会って確かめてみたい
I want to meet you and find out for sure
世界のことわり　愛の定義
The logic of the world, the definition of love
幸せのカテゴリー
The category of happiness
まだまだ君を知りたい
I still want to know you more
こんなセリフ柄でもないけど
A line like this isn't my style, but...
どんなに格好つけてたって始まりやしない
No matter how much I act cool, nothing will start
君じゃなきゃダメみたい
It seems it has to be you
Cutie Panther
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
どこにいるの？
Where are you?
ムリよムリよ
It's no use, no use
どこにいたってムリよ
Wherever you are, it's no use
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
だれといるの？
Who are you with?
ダメよダメよ
No, no
私以外はダメよ
Anyone but me is no good
甘いよ甘い そんな装備じゃ
How sweet, how sweet, with such equipment
逃げられるわけないじゃないか
There's no way you can escape
狙いをつけて 密かに
Taking aim, secretly
横から
From the side
I love you
私のことを好きになるはず
You're bound to fall for me
I love you
そこに正義があるの
That's where justice lies
何度も言わせるつもりなの？
How many times do I have to say it?
あおやあおや
Oh my, oh my
抵抗するなしでごらん
Try not to resist
はいはいはい
Yes, yes, yes
我がままだと知ってるけれど
I know I'm selfish
私の方が上手なようね
But it seems I'm the superior one
冷たい言葉
Cold words
優しい視線
A gentle gaze
獲物は...
The prey is...
君だよ！
You!
Cutie Panther 私は
I'm the Cutie Panther
どこでも行くよ
I'll go anywhere
君の 君の
Your, your
心盗んでみせるよ
Heart, I'll steal it
Cutie Panther 私は
I'm the Cutie Panther
どこでも行くよ
I'll go anywhere
君の 君の
Your, your
心を離さない
I won't let your heart go
熱いよ熱い 愛のルールは
It's hot, it's hot, the rules of love
破られるためあるんだよ
Exist to be broken
狡い笑いと意外な
A sly laugh and an unexpected
微笑みは
Smile
I miss you
好きのせいだし悪くないでしょ
It's because of love, so it's not bad, right?
I miss you
それが重度の恋よ
That's a serious case of love
絶対手に入れてみせるよ
I'll definitely make you mine
おやおや
Oh dear, oh dear
抵抗するなしでごらん
Try not to resist
はいはいはい
Yes, yes, yes
偽りだって疑うよりも
Rather than doubting it's a lie
私のこと信じてみてよ
Just try believing in me
優しい言葉
Gentle words
冷たい視線
A cold gaze
獲物は...
The prey is...
君だよ！
You!
Cutie Panther 君の
Cutie Panther, your
瞳が欲しい
Eyes, I want them
私 きっと
I'll surely
きっと盗んでみせるよ
Surely steal them
Cutie Panther 君の
Cutie Panther, your
瞳が欲しい
Eyes, I want them
私 きっと
I'll surely
素早く逃がさない
Quickly not let you escape
何度も言わせるつもりなの？
How many times do I have to say it?
あおやあおや
Oh my, oh my
抵抗するなしでごらん
Try not to resist
はいはいはい
Yes, yes, yes
我がままだと知ってるけれど
I know I'm selfish
私の方が上手なようね
But it seems I'm the superior one
冷たい言葉
Cold words
優しい視線
A gentle gaze
獲物は...
The prey is...
君だよ！
You!
Cutie Panther 私は
I'm the Cutie Panther
どこでも行くよ
I'll go anywhere
君の 君の
Your, your
心盗んでみせるよ
Heart, I'll steal it
Cutie Panther 私は
I'm the Cutie Panther
どこでも行くよ
I'll go anywhere
君の 君の
Your, your
心を離さない
I won't let your heart go
どこにいるの？
Where are you?
ムリよムリよ
It's no use, no use
どこにいたってムリよ
Wherever you are, it's no use
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
だれといるの？
Who are you with?
ダメよダメよ
No, no
私以外はダメよ
Anyone but me is no good
どこにいるの？
Where are you?
ムリよムリよ
It's no use, no use
どこにいたってムリよ
Wherever you are, it's no use
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
だれといるの？
Who are you with?
ダメよダメよ
No, no
私以外はダメよ
Anyone but me is no good
キセキ
作詞・作曲：GReeeeN
Kiseki
Lyrics & Composition: GReeeeN
明日、今日よりも好きになれる
Tomorrow, I'll love you even more than today
溢れる想いが止まらない
These overflowing feelings won't stop
今もこんなに好きでいるのに
Even though I love you this much right now
言葉に出来ない
I can't put it into words
君のくれた日々が積み重なり
The days you gave me piled up
過ぎ去った日々 2人歩いた『軌跡』
The days that passed, the 'path' we two walked
僕らの出逢いがもし偶然ならば?
If our meeting was just a coincidence?
運命ならば? 君に巡り合えた それって『奇跡』
If it was fate? That I could meet you, that's a 'miracle'
2人寄り添って歩いて 永久の愛を形にして
Walking close together, giving form to eternal love
いつまでも君の横で 笑っていたくて
I want to be laughing by your side forever
アリガトウや Ah 愛してるじゃまだ
Saying 'Thank you' or 'I love you' is still...
足りないけどせめて言わせて 「幸せです」と
...not enough, but at least let me say, "I'm happy"
いつも君の右の手のひらを
Always, your right palm...
ただ僕の左の手のひらが
...is just held by my left palm
そっと包んでくそれだけで
Just by gently wrapping around it
ただ愛を感じていた
I felt nothing but love
日々の中で 小さな幸せ
In the middle of our days, small bits of happiness
見つけ重ね ゆっくり歩いた『軌跡』
Finding and piling them up, the 'path' we walked slowly
僕らの出逢いは大きな世界で
Our meeting, in this big world
小さな出来事 巡り合えた それって『奇跡』
Is a small event, but meeting you, that's a 'miracle'
うまく行かない日だって 2人で居れば晴れだって
Even on days when things don't go well, if we're together it's sunny
強がりや寂しさも 忘れられるから
Because I can forget my bluffing and loneliness
僕は君でなら 僕でいれるから!
Because if it's you, I can be myself!
だからいつもそばに居てよ 『愛しい君へ』
So please stay by my side always, 'to my beloved'
2人ふざけあった帰り道
On the way home when the two of us were fooling around
それも大切な僕らの日々
Those too are our precious days
「想いよ届け!!!」と伝えた時に
When I said, "Let my feelings reach you!!!"
初めて見せた表情の君
The expression you showed for the first time
少し間が空いて 君がうなずいて
A small silence, then you nodded
僕らの心 満たされてく愛で
Our hearts were being filled with love
僕らまだ旅の途中で
We're still in the middle of our journey
またこれから先も何十年
And for decades to come
続いていけるような未来へ
Towards a future that can continue
2人寄り添って歩いて 永久の愛を形にして
Walking close together, giving form to eternal love
いつまでも君の横で 笑っていたくて
I want to be laughing by your side forever
アリガトウや Ah 愛してるじゃまだ
Saying 'Thank you' or 'I love you' is still...
足りないけどせめて言わせて 「幸せです」と
...not enough, but at least let me say, "I'm happy"
うまく行かない日だって 2人で居れば晴れだって
Even on days when things don't go well, if we're together it's sunny
喜びや悲しみも 全て分け合える
We can share all the joy and sadness
君が居るから 生きていけるから!
Because you're here, because I can keep living!
だからいつもそばに居てよ 『愛しい君へ』
So please stay by my side always, 'to my beloved'
最後の一秒まで
Until the very last second
明日、今日より笑顔になれる
Tomorrow, I can smile even more than today
君が居るだけで そう思えるから
Just because you're here, I can think so
何十年 何百年 何千年 時を越えよう
For decades, centuries, millennia, let's cross time
君を愛してる
I love you
ここで告知セカァアアアアン！！
Now for the announcement section!!
今年も出ます！兎田ぺこら誕生日記念グッズ2024！イェーイ！
This year too, Usada Pekora Birthday Celebration Goods 2024 are coming! Yay!
まずはラインナップはこちら！ドーン！
First, here is the lineup! Ta-da!
今回はライブのテーマでもある学校グッズ！
This time it's school goods, which is also the theme of the live!
これを手にするだけで、UPアカデミー生になれる！
Just by getting these, you can become a UP Academy student!
じゃあ、ひとつずつ見ていくぺこ！ひとつ目はこちら！
Let's look at them one by one, peko! First one is this!
卒業証書！
Graduation certificate!
卒業証書 / イラスト：憂姫はぐれ
Graduation Certificate / Illustration: Hagure Yuki
ひょーひょー！いや、すぐ卒業するかい！
Hyo-hyo! No, graduating already?!
なんと入学1日で、U.P.アカデミーは卒業できちゃうぺこなんでっす。
Surprisingly, you can graduate from U.P. Academy in just one day.
グッズでね、ちょっと卒業証書とかって珍しくて、いいぺこだなーとか思いつつも、
In terms of goods, a graduation certificate is a bit unusual and I thought it was nice...
見てください、はぐれママが描いたぺこちゃん！
Look at this Peko-chan drawn by Hagure-mama!
もう綺麗、可愛い、最高ぺこです！
It's beautiful, cute, and just the best!
しかも、この卒業証書は棚とかにね、飾れるぺこなんで、是非とも飾っていただきたい！
What's more, this graduation certificate can be displayed on a shelf, so please do display it!
そして、二つ目は、こちら！
And the second one is this!
ぺこーらの学習帳 / イラスト：おくに(ん)
Pekora's Notebook / Illustration: Okunin
ぺこーらの学習帳！
Pekora's Notebook!
これで、たくさん勉強や落書きをしてほしいぺこ。イラストはおくに(ん)先生です。
I want you to use this for lots of studying and doodling. The illustration is by Okunin-sensei.
表紙の裏には、なんと！なんと！なんと！なんと！なんと！ぺこちゃんの新作ポエムがあるみたいぺこ！
On the inside of the cover, surprisingly! Peko-chan has a new poem!
このために、ぺこら、何作品か提出させていただきました。是非ともお楽しみに！
For this, I, Pekora, submitted several works. Please look forward to it!
まぁ、このノートをね、学校でも会社でもお家でも、たくさん使ってほしいぺこー。
Well, I want you to use this notebook a lot, whether at school, work, or home.
続いて、三つ目は、こちら！
Next, the third one is this!
おでかけぬいぐるみキーホルダー
Odekake Plushie Keyholder
かわいいーーー！！
So cute!!
白うさぎの着ぐるみを着た、ぺこらの、おでかけぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
An Odekake Plushie Keyholder of Pekora wearing a white rabbit costume!
ま、カバンとかに付けてね、たくさん色々なところに連れて行ってほしいぺこ。
Well, please attach it to your bag and take me to many different places.
ぺこら、なかなかね、家から出ないので、是非ともこのぬいぐるみキーホルダーを連れて行って、ぺこらが、うん、どっか旅行行った感じの、気分になれるようにしてほしいぺこです。
Pekora doesn't go out much, so please take this plushie keyholder with you and make me feel like I've gone on a trip.
しかも、この表情も、たまらない...
And this expression is just irresistible...
そして、四つ目は、こちら！
And the fourth one is this!
トートバッグ
Tote Bag
U.P.アカデミーのトートバッグ！
U.P. Academy Tote Bag!
さっきの、おでかけぬいぐるみキーホルダーを付けたら、もう完璧！
If you attach the earlier Odekake Plushie Keyholder, it's perfect!
このトートバッグはシンプルな形なので、めちゃめちゃ使いやすいぺこ。
This tote bag has a simple shape, so it's very easy to use.
そして、そしてよ、U.P.アカデミーの、このロゴ！見てよ、めちゃめちゃお洒落だし、もう学生気分も味わえちゃう。
And, and, this logo of U.P. Academy! Look at it, it's so stylish and you can feel like a student.
ま、色々なね、用途で使えると思うぺこなんで、たくさん使ってくれると嬉しいぺこです。
Well, I think it can be used for various purposes, so I'd be happy if you use it a lot.
フルセット購入特典
Full Set Purchase Bonus
そして、こちら、フルセット購入してくれた方には、
And for those who purchase the full set,
箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りのポストカードが付いてくるぺこ！
it comes with a postcard featuring a foil-stamped signature and message!
表情もね、ニコリとして、かわいいぺこちゃんなんで、
The expression is also a cute, smiling Peko-chan.
あとあと、メッセージも、なんて書かれてくるか、お楽しみにーー！！
And also, please look forward to seeing what's written in the message!!
フルセット以外にもね、単品でも買えるので、気に入ってくれた方は、是非とも手に取ってもらえると嬉しいぺこ。
Besides the full set, they're also available individually, so I'd be happy if you could get them if you like them.
販売時間は、このライブが終わった、10時からぺこです。是非ともやらぺこー！
Sales start from 10:00 PM, after this live ends. Yara-peko!
U.P.アカデミーへのね、入学お待ちしてまーす！
We're looking forward to your enrollment at U.P. Academy!
そして、そして、この後10時15分からは、
And then, from 10:15 PM today,
メンバー限定アンコールLIVE
Member-Only Encore Live
メンバー限定の、アンコールライブがあるぺこーー！！
there will be a member-only encore live!!
何の曲を歌うのかなー？踊るのかなー？
What songs will I sing? Will I dance?
メンバーの方は、そちらもお楽しみに！
Members, please look forward to that too!
ぺこーらありがとうLive
Pekora Arigato Live
それでは、ぺこーらありがとうライブは、ここまで！
Well then, that's all for the Pekora Arigato Live!
見てくれた人、本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much to everyone who watched!
これからも、やらぺこー！
Let's keep up the Pekora spirit!
また、次の配信で、お会いしましょう！
See you in the next stream!
バイバーーーイ！
Bye-bye!